<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>UCLA Chi Epsilon</title>
    <link>https://uclachiepsilon.github.io/</link>
    <description>Recent content on UCLA Chi Epsilon</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    
	<atom:link href="https://uclachiepsilon.github.io/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Events</title>
      <link>https://uclachiepsilon.github.io/events/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://uclachiepsilon.github.io/events/</guid>
      <description>Events       </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Initiates</title>
      <link>https://uclachiepsilon.github.io/initiates/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://uclachiepsilon.github.io/initiates/</guid>
      <description>Initiate Central  Check Progress  Detailed Instructions    Initiates must complete the following requirements related to the fundamental pillars of Chi Epsilon before being granted membership. The four pillars — which we consider to be the primary traits of a successful engineer — are Scholarship, Character, Practicality, and Sociability.
The candidate is responsible for tracking their own progress through documents supplemented by the Marshal. An initiate need only notify the Marshal of their completed activity.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Join</title>
      <link>https://uclachiepsilon.github.io/join/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://uclachiepsilon.github.io/join/</guid>
      <description>Chi Epsilon at UCLA  Join Us  Chi Epsilon seeks to foster excellence, connectivity and engagement among those in the civil engineering community to improve our world, and we are always happy to help qualified members become a part of this society.
National Chi Epsilon    Why Join?  Your achievement in scholastic endeavors is recognized and appreciated. Chi Epsilon is no obscure honors society; it is the National Civil Engineering Honor Society.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Members</title>
      <link>https://uclachiepsilon.github.io/members/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://uclachiepsilon.github.io/members/</guid>
      <description>Members &amp; Alumni  -- Current Members Class of 2021Ali ShumailaClass of 2022Amaya HernandezClass of 2023Amy ZhouClass of 2021Anjali SwamyClass of 2022Brian LingClass of 2022Bryant YangClass of 2021Camryn LopezClass of 2023Emily TranClass of 2022Emma GolubClass of 2021Eric EstradaClass of 2021Haochen SunClass of 2023Jackie LimClass of 2022Justin EhrenbergerClass of 2023Kathryn HoangClass of 2023Kelly EspinoClass of 2022Luca CordovaClass of 2023Mayra LaraClass of 2024Michael DuClass of 2022Nathan VardasClass of 2021Peter LeeClass of 2024Rahul PalClass of 2021Rodger LeeClass of 2022Saed OsmanClass of 2022Sophia TanClass of 2021Stacy KongClass of 2023Tiffany ChoiClass of 2024Tricia JainClass of 2024Wendy ChauClass of 2021Yuen Lenh Alumni  Fall 2020 Ali ShumailaClass of 2021 Amy ZhouClass of 2023 Justin EhrenbergerClass of 2022 Tiffany ChoiClass of 2023  Spring 2021 Bryant YangClass of 2022 Jackie LimClass of 2023 Michael DuClass of 2024 Rahul PalClass of 2024 Tricia JainClass of 2024 Wendy ChauClass of 2024    Fall 2019 Eric EstradaClass of 2021 Joceline SuhaimiClass of 2020 Rodger LeeClass of 2021  Spring 2020 Amaya HernandezClass of 2022 Brian LingClass of 2022 Emily TranClass of 2023 Emma GolubClass of 2022 Kathryn HoangClass of 2023 Kelly EspinoClass of 2023 Luca CordovaClass of 2022 Mayra LaraClass of 2023 Nathan VardasClass of 2022 Peter LeeClass of 2021 Saed OsmanClass of 2022 Sophia TanClass of 2022    Fall 2018 Abby EdwardsClass of 2020 Anjali SwamyClass of 2021 Arya NandaClass of 2021 Claire KillianClass of 2020 Elizabeth PazClass of 2021 Joshua GrahamClass of 2020 Liz MenendezClass of 2020 Megan OliverosClass of 2020 Nick BrownClass of 2020 Rahaf BarrkoudiClass of 2020 Stacy KongClass of 2021 Tsandi ChenClass of 2020 Yuen LenhClass of 2021  Spring 2019 Camryn LopezClass of 2021 Natalia RamirezClass of 2020 Sara Abou KorroumClass of 2020    Fall 2017 Siddhant JainClass of 2019 Yash KansalClass of 2019  Spring 2018 Bryan OngClass of 2019 Jonathan TaiClass of 2020 Kyle SampleClass of 2020 Lew Xuan YuClass of 2019 Pauline NguyenClass of 2019 Zac PuckettClass of 2020    Fall 2016 Amberly BarkClass of 2018 Emma SuchardClass of 2018 John SchmidtClass of 2019 Jonathan SongClass of 2019 Julianna BurkeClass of 2018 Kyle EvansClass of 2017 Nathan De RoppClass of 2018 Rayan FardounClass of 2018 Samantha FungClass of 2017 Zohair ZulfiqarClass of 2018  Spring 2017 Ada ChangClass of 2019 Arielle SanghviClass of 2018 Bryan HongClass of 2019 Caileen YuClass of 2020 Daniel HendricksClass of 2017 Lauren PoseyClass of 2020 Sidney PoonClass of 2019    Fall 2015 Abbie BenderClass of 2016 Alis ChhayClass of 2016 Asia ReevesClass of 2018 Cayla WhitesideClass of 2018 Eric RobertsClass of 2018 Haoxiang MiaoClass of 2016 Mingjie ZhaoClass of 2016 Nolan CooneyClass of 2017 Ryan RizeqClass of 2018  Spring 2016 Abigail ChungClass of 2017 Chu Young WooClass of 2018 Ernesto Martinez-PazClass of 2016 Evan SchulzClass of 2018 Hadiza FelicienClass of 2017    Fa11 2014 Abigail GunningClass of 2016 An GaoClass of 2016 Bartu ErdemliClass of 2016 Ira Kathryn NoblejasClass of 2016 Sierra KennisonClass of 2016 Zachary McFannClass of 2016  Spring 2015 Blake WyattClass of 2017 Christopher JansenClass of 2016 Ismael EscobedoClass of 2017 Jerry ChenClass of 2017 Megan NazarenoClass of 2017 Morolake OmoyaClass of 2016 Ryan WorleyClass of 2017 Timothy FairleyClass of 2016 Suraj PatelClass of 2017 Trenton SaundersClass of 2016 Vincent SorrentinoClass of 2015    Fall 2013 Andrew KennedyClass of 2015 Clint BannoutClass of 2015 Chao-Chun YangClass of 2015 Elynor ZhouClass of 2015 Kevin SandClass of 2015 Mark DuongClass of 2015 Tiffany HoClass of 2014 Norman ChakClass of 2015 Sung LeeClass of 2015 Weng Cheong SinClass of 2015 Yinan PeiClass of 2015 Ziyi LianClass of 2015  Spring 2014 Alicia PedneaultClass of 2016 Gabriel Felipe ConcepcionClass of 2016 Hyun Dong KimClass of 2014 Maxwell ArmentaClass of 2016 Michael Daciolas-SemonClass of 2015 Patrick DonovanClass of 2015 Rajaa AlrayyesClass of 2016    Fall 2012 Adena NikarakelyanClass of 2013 Anthony Ambrosia-MeirClass of 2015 Armen AzizianClass of 2014 Charlotte InsullClass of 2013 Christopher LeeClass of 2014 Dorian KrauszClass of 2014 Evelyn BarkhordarianClass of 2014 Jacquelyn GentesClass of 2014 Kevin SantosClass of 2013 Maayan CoganClass of 2014 Melissa ChristiansenClass of 2014 Reisa SoedarsonoClass of 2014 Rhonda El-HachacheClass of 2015 Tandre OeyClass of 2014  Spring 2013 Boanne SongClass of 2014 Brandon PangClass of 2015 Casey LeClass of 2015 Justen QuanClass of 2015 Laura McNerneyClass of 2014 Michael TsaiClass of 2015 Samuel Zabb-ParmleyClass of 2015 Skyler FerryClass of 2015     </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Officers</title>
      <link>https://uclachiepsilon.github.io/officers/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://uclachiepsilon.github.io/officers/</guid>
      <description>Officers   Camryn LopezPresidentCamryn Lopez is a senior civil engineering major interested in pursuing a career in hydrology. She currently works as an intern for a civil engineering company learning about the design of civil infrastructure. Camryn is also passionate about supporting and encouraging women in STEM through the Society of Women Engineers (SWE) and outreach. Outside of the classroom, she enjoys dancing, tennis, and crocheting.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>